

Hi! I'm Kunal Khurana, a soil physicist with more than 10 years of working experience in agronomy, soil fertility, and plant nutrition. I gained this experience by working at different geographic locations of the world on diverse projects with different experts. I am particularly passionate about working with AI and machine learning professionals to fight against climate change by storing more amount of C in the soil and saving precious water.

Education

2021 Francisation et Intégration au Milieu Québécois Université Laval, CA

2016 | Master's in Soil Science | Punjab Agricultural University, IN

2013 Bachelor's in Agriculture Punjabi University Patiala, IN

Work Experience

September 2022 – December 2023 Researcher, McGill University

September 2020 – November 2020 | Freelance Translator, Cerda

January 2019 – June 2022 Research Assistant, Université Laval

October 2016 – December 2018 Research Fellow, Punjab Agricultural University

Let's Connect!

One of my greatest motivations for creating online content is to engage with fascinating individuals from all over the world. If you're interested in having a chat, feel free to reach out to me. I would love to hear from you!